// flashcards/b738specslimits.js
export const b738specslimits = [
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the center fuel tank capacity", back: "30,500 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: How many crash axes and where are they located?", back: "1; in the cockpit" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the service ceiling?", back: "41,000 MSL" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum zero fuel weight? (MZFW)", back: "136,000 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum takeoff weight? (MTOW)", back: "174,200 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the minimum runway width?", back: "148'" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: Can you have a planned fuel imbalance between the two wing tanks?", back: "NO" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: How much fuel can each wing tank hold?", back: "9,100 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum runway up/downslope permitted?", back: "±2%" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum operating altitude with both AC PACKs inoperative?", back: "10,000' MSL" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: Runway Contaminates, what types and quantities will prevent taking off safely?", back: "<ul>" +
         "<li>Less than <b>3</b>\" of dry snow</li>" +
         "<li>Less than <b>1/2</b>\" of wet snow</li>" +
         "<li>Less than <b>1/2</b>\" of slush</li>" +
         "<li>Less than <b>1/2</b>\" of standing water</li>" +
         "<li>Chunks of hardened snow or ice</li>" +
         "</ul>"},
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum cruise speed (Critical Mach Number)", back: "Mach 0.82" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum outside air temperature for takeoff (in Celsius)", back: "54°C" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the minimum outside air temperature for takeoff (in Celsius)", back: "-54°C" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum distance an alternate can be from the departure airport?", back: "320 NM" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: How many emergency exits and where are they located?", back: "<p><b>10:</b></p><ul><li>2 - Cockpit Windows</li><li>2 - Forward Galley Doors (L1/R1)</li><li>4 - Over-wing Windows</li><li>2 - Aft Galley Doors (L2/R2)</li></ul>" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum unplanned fuel imbalance between the wing tanks?", back: "1,000 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum allowable crosswind without winglets?", back: "36 kts" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum allowable crosswind with winglets?", back: "33 kts" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What altitude must the AC descend to after an in-flight pressure loss? How quickly must it get there?", back: "14,000' MSL within 4 minutes" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum field elevation for takeoff?", back: "8,400' MSL" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum ramp/taxi weight?", back: "174,700 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum allowed tailwind for landing?", back: "10 kts" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the empty/basic operating weight? (BOW)", back: "96,100 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: How much thrust does each engine produce?", back: "26,400 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the allowable CG range as a percentage of MAC?", back: "Between 6% to 32%<br>(<b>M</b>ean <b>A</b>erodynamic <b>C</b>hord)" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What is the maximum landing weight? (MLW)", back: "144,000 LBS" },
	{ front: "Boeing 737-800: What altitude is the AC pressurized to?", back: "8000'" },
];